史蒂文VS紫晶
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
牙牙/饼干一枚
校对
linn/husky/右翼部鸣明
特效
presisco
压制
填字：右翼部鸣明   Matisse 文本处理：谷子
时间轴：SGcat
呃...我觉得我们永远找不到铁石英了
We're never going to find Jasper.
珍珠 石榴
Pearl, Garnet!
我们找到铁石英了
We found Jasper!
啥
What?!
我们打败她了!
We beat her!
天惹噜
Oh, my gosh!
你还好吧 发生了什么
Are you all right?! What happened?!
她和那些巨大的雪怪一起出现了
She showed up with those big snow monsters,
我们和她战斗了
so we fought those.
但是战斗越来越激烈-所以我和康妮合体了
But then things got really scary, so Connie and I fused!
史蒂翁妮骑着狮子赶跑了铁石英
Stevonnie got to ride lion and we chased Jasper away!
你们的所有训练-让你们干的超棒
All your training -- you did so well!
我们为你自豪
We're so proud of you.
等等,紫晶去哪了
Wait. Where's Amethyst?
呦-呦
yo-Yo.
紫晶...?
Amethyst?
你又重生了
You reformed.
我好着呢
I'm fine.
我想你已经为你一周一次的训练准备好了 史蒂文
I hope you're ready for your weekly training, Steven!
我准备好了
I'm ready -- on the weekly!
你已经取得了一次胜利
You've had one victory,
但现在有更多次对抗铁石英的战斗
but there are more fights to come now that Jasper's --
现在铁石英已经---
Now that Jasper's --
现在铁石英已经卷土重来 让我们加油训练吧
Jasper's back! Let's work hard!
嘿 紫晶
Hey, Amethyst.
怎么了
Yo.
你想来看我训练吗
You want to come watch me train?
不要
Can't.
我忙着做鸡蛋沙拉呢
I'm busy making egg salad.
别酱嘛～这会很有趣的
Come on, it'll be fun!
唔...
Mm...
你可以看我怎样得到珍珠点
You'll get to see me earn Pearl points.
珍珠点是啥
What are Pearl points?
很高兴你问我了
I'm glad you asked!
我要把这些珍珠点奖励给
Pearl: Pearl points are awarded
那些珍正坚持不懈并积极向上并珍惜时间的人
for punctuality, perseverance, and positivity.
我们也许比我们的对手
We may be smaller, weaker, and less gifted
更弱小 更没有天赋 但只要有了这些珍珠点奖励
---than our opponents, but with these "P"s,
我们就有了成功的钥匙
we have the keys to success.
以及-----可以得到珍数袋里的奖品
And -- to the Pearl prize pouch!
噗噗 珍了不起
Ha! P-amazing
谢啦
Thank you.
有这口袋里有一些东西珍不错
There's some P-great stuff in that pouch.
上一周 我得到了这个
Last week, I got these!
我甚至都不需要眼镜 所以这超好玩
I don't even need glasses, so it's funny!
港真 紫晶 这些小礼物真是
Really, Amethyst, the positive reinforcement
起到了很大作用
has been doing wonders.
我也想加入
I want in.
加入玩眼镜的行列吗
On the glasses?
不 我要加入训练
On the training.
真的
Really?
紫晶你
You, Amethyst?
当然了 你懂的 为了找乐子
Yeah. You know, for fun.
太棒辣 热烈欢迎
All right!
好了好了 别客气
Yeah, yeah.  You're welcome.
那么 我们开始训练吧
Well, then, let the training begin!
测试的第一关是速度
Your first test will be speed.
为了让你们更好的训练
To aid your training,
我将会用全息珍珠来进行考验
I will be utilizing my holograms.
欢迎使用全息珍珠第2.000001版
Welcome to Holo-Pearl version 2.000001.
我改造了她们
I've modified them
为了让她们习惯轻松的训练
to accommodate less lethal training.
人心才是最锋利的武器
The sharpest weapon is the mind.
全息珍珠将会在竞技场的边缘
The Holo-Pearl will serve as a checkpoint
充当一个检查站
at the edge of the arena.
每跑完一个来回就和全息珍珠击掌作为记号
Mark your lap with a Holo-Pearl high five.
接收 击掌
High five accepted!
两个来回 两次击掌
Two laps, two fives.
胜者就会得到一个珍珠点
One pearl point to the winner!
懂啦
Got it!
知道了
Yerp.
好啦 各就各位----
Okay then, on your marks.
预备---
Ready...
稳住---
steady...
开跑
go!
接收 击掌
High five accepted
哇哦...
Huh?
接受 击掌
High five accepted
来击掌庆祝一下吧 紫晶(接收 击掌)
Give me digits, Amethyst! High five accepted!
史蒂文得到了一个珍珠点
One point for Steven already!
干得好 紫晶
Good thinking, Amethyst.
放点水让他建立信心
Going easy on him will build his confidence!
呵 我还能说什么
What can I say,
我处处让着他
I'm a natural at going easy.
你们的下一门测试是敏捷
Pearl: Your next test is agility.
你们要想尽办法去躲避长矛
Dodge the spears the best you can.
噢
Agh!
已被击败
Defeat accepted!
哇哦...
Whoa.
胜利 胜利
Victory, victory!
别太让着他了 他依然需要锻炼
Don't go too easy on him. He still needs a challenge.
现在 你们面临的是最后一门测试 全面战斗
And now, for your final test, an all-out battle.
这是对你们所掌握技能的最终测定
This is the ultimate determination of your skills!
预备 开始
Okay! Ready, go!
来打我啊 你们这些全息混蛋
Come and get me, you holo-punks!
啊
Aah!
唔
Mm.
别躲了 让我赢
Stop moving so I can win!
多谢 哈
Thanks. Wah!
回旋飞盾
Boomerang shield!
已被击败*4
-Defeat accepted! -Defeat accepted!
完胜
Victory accepted!
恭喜你 史蒂文
Congratulations, Steven!
你赢得了最后的珍珠点
You earn the final point!
是时候奖励你珍数袋里的奖品了
It's time for you to pick a prize from the prize pouch!
浪人孤刃vs元气拳手
Man:Lonely Blade versus Outgoing Fist.
第一回合 开始
Round 1 -- fight!
飞拳攻击
Flying punch!
回旋飞剑!*3!!!(暴击)
Boomerang, boomerang, boomerang blade!
K.O.
就连我的拳头也死的透透的
Even my fists are dead!
嘿紫晶 你想和我来一局孤刃吗
Hey, Amethyst, do you want to play "Lonely Blade" with me?
我帮你把手柄捂热了
I warmed up the controller for you.
好呀
Yeah, all right.
浪人孤刃有了新版本
There's a new costume for Lonely Blade --
紫晶与史蒂文的手柄与Gamecube相同
蓝版孤刃
Blue Lonely Blade!
你应该用这个角色
You should play as him!
随便啦
Whatevie.
界面中GWOOD GUY出自"铁拳"系列的木人,右下角的北极熊则来自同门的"咱们裸熊"
浪人孤刃双重对决
Lonely Blade versus Lonely Blade!
我的刀刃 是这片大陆上最好的
My blade is the best in all the land.
一回合 杀
Round 1 -- fight!
回旋飞剑
Boomerang, blade!
啊 这真是够了
Ugh, this is tough.
那鬼条条一直都在那里吗
Were those bars always there?
你说的是HP框 对啊
The health bars? Yeah.
行吧 行吧
Right, right...
嗷 你打的可真好
Ugh! You're doing so well!
我还用一个月的时间去尝试连击
I've been trying to master that combo for months!
你做到了 一次性的
You got it in, like, one try!
哦我的妈妈咪呀 我根本没有办法击败你
Oh, man! There's no way I could beat you!
千影刃
1,000 mirror blade!
吧咋黑
Hyah!
K.O.
K.O.!
毕竟我的刀是孤独的
My blade is the loneliest after all.
那可真是太厉害了 紫晶
That was crazy good, Amethyst.
打得好啊
Nice job!
够了史蒂文 我知道你是故意让我赢的
Knock it off Steven, I know you let me win.
啥 我听不懂 我没有啊
What, me? No!
我内什么...
I...
才没有做呢
No.
你甚至没有尽力
You weren't even trying.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我只是想让你感觉好一些
I just wanted you to feel better.
太--好了 就算是现在的你都比我成熟太多
Great. And now you're even more mature than me.
紫晶
Amethyst?
你应该是个菜鸟
You're supposed to be the rookie,
但是现在的你无论在哪件事上都做的比我好
but now you're better than me at everything.
我现在就是最差劲的宝石战士
Now I'm the worst crystal gem.
啥 啥玩意儿
W-What?
呃啊 你知道我啥意思 史蒂文
Ugh! You know what I mean, Steven.
呃额 并不
Uh, not really!
然后我做到了 你在生我的气
And now I am, and you're mad at me?!
不 我是生我自己的气
No! I get mad at myself!
就是 哈啊 就是因为我做的事
That's, ugh, the thing I do.
我在生我自己的气
I get mad at myself,
不管我在什么事上做太多都会让我变得很腊鸡
and then it makes me suck at everything I do even more!
紫晶 你一点都不腊鸡
Amethyst, you don't suck.
你做过许多特帅的事
You do so many cool things.
你有俩条鞭子啊 俩条啊
You have two whips -- two whips!
还有冲刺也很厉害啊
And the dash thing?!
紫晶 你有太多比我好的地方
Amethyst, you're so much better than me.
不可能 你有玫瑰的盾
No way. You have Rose's shield.
还有泡泡 你还可以上天
And Bubble! And the floating thing!
还有 呃啊 如果是我我就成天在天上飘着了
And, ugh, I'd just be floating all day!
上天 我很多时候都忘了我有这个能力
Floating? I forget to use that half the time!
在剩下的那些时间里
And the rest of the time,
我根本就不能好好使用能力
my powers aren't even guaranteed to work!
我...我有些地方比你还腊鸡
I'm... I'm way worse than you.
啊哈 我最腊鸡
Nuh-uh. I'm the worst!
不 我最腊鸡 我会证明它
No way! I am! I'll prove it!
我要-我要和你干一架来证明我有多差劲
I'll-I'll fight you and show you how bad I am!
来啊 来干啊
Fine! Let's do it!
让最差的宝石战士输掉
Let the worst gem lose!
道理很简单 我会在最长的时间里输掉
Get ready, I'm about to lose big time!
不会让你得逞的
No way!
我一定会被揍得特惨以至于我都不知道我怎么被打的
I'm gonna get clobbered so bad , I won't know what hit me!
没有啥套路
No holding back?
No holding back!
搞毛
What?
嚯哈
Ooh-wah!
哦啊
Whoa!
我根本就没有看到那招来了
I did not see that coming!
那太帅了
That was amazing!
不
No, it's not!
我不会在做啥厉害事儿了
I don't do anything amazing!
你才是最厉害的
You're the one who's amazing!
哦呜呜呜呜啊
Whoa!
搞毛 新招
What?! Is that new?
哇哦 那可真棒!
Because it's awesome!
不 它的出现是个意外
No, it was an accident!
意外一点也不·棒
Accidents are not awesome!
可以 这很强势
Sure. Right!
史蒂文的飞踢招式源自"假面骑士"的招牌终结技
吭
Huh?
搞毛 别救
What?! Don't save --
哇哦 那可真厉害
Whoa! That was great!
你以为这就是我做的吗
You think that was on purpose?
猜猜谁记得上
Guess who remembered to floa--
呜哦
Whoa!
史蒂文
Steven?
看到没 我把你从天上扯下来了
See?! I dropped you from the sky,
但你快要用石头赢了我
but you almost just won using a rock!
嚯 如果我不能打败你我就永远不能打败铁石英
Huh! If I can't beat you, I'm never going to beat Jasper!
你完全可以打败我
You! You can totally beat me!
你基本没有去爆发洪荒之力
You're not even trying!
我爆发了
I am, too!
哈
Huh?!
我认为我们在不合格的战士这块儿做的挺不错的
I think we're both too good at being bad fighters.
那是你认为的
That's what you think!
你什么意思.
What does that even mean?
什么意思都没有
I don't even know!
咱俩到底哪根筋搭错了啊
What's wrong with us?!
嗯 我知道那筋在我身上搭错了
Well, I know what's wrong with me.
我不是那么的弱小
I'm not supposed to be small,
但每个人都好像没这事一样
and everyone's always acting like there's no problem.
你想做什么就做什么
"You can be anything you want to be."
不 我不行
No, I can't!
我根本不能成为我应该成为的样子 你懂
I can't even be the one thing I'm supposed to be, ya know?
当然懂
Of course I do.
我不是玫瑰石英
I'm not rose quartz.
哦别 哦史蒂文
Oh, no. Oh, Steven.
你为什么认为我工作很努力
Why do you think I've been working so hard?
哦 付出就会有回报
Well, it's paying off.
我希望是如此
I sure hope so!
谢了 史蒂文
Thanks, Steven.
Aaa 你俩个在搞啥啊
Aah! What did you two do?
你们居然能把废墟破坏了
You've ruined the ruins!
哎呀
Whoops.
我不觉得这段时间我们能看到那个奖袋了
I don't think we're gonna see that prize pouch for a while.